[Applause]
[Music]
now let us begin with question number
seven number seven did you buy this
jacket at a
discount a they're in the men's
department b a winter ski
vacation see yes it was half off
number eight who left the laptop in the
break room a no I'll keep
working B Mr Rose
did C you can borrow
mine number nine where can I pick up
luggage from flight
521 a to take a business trip B it
departs in half an
hour C at baggage carousel
3 number 10 when will the vice president
return from the board
meeting a check with his
assistant B Yes we made a lot of
decisions C in conference room B
number 11 how can I prepare for the
interview a there's a great View From
Here B by researching the
company C she thinks she got the
job number 12 why can't I use the
parking
lot a sure except for holidays
B no I took the
bus C because it is now being
repaved number 13 are you free to cover
my shift on
Friday a I'll be out of town B who was
it C the daily specials please
number 14 what's your opinion on the new
website
design a thanks for visiting it B no I
read it in the
newspaper C I like its modern
look number 15 the light in the corridor
is still
broken a we'd better inform maintenance
again
B it hasn't been decided
yet C yes we need to change our
marketing
strategy number 16 could I get a few
extra tickets for the technology
Workshop a an expert in the
field B sorry but it's sold
out see the performance was amazing
number 17 when will our banners be ready
to pick up a at least
$25 B let's call The Print Shop to
ask C oh is that what he
said number 18 this washing machine has
a water saving cycle right a I've been
watching it B at the appliance store in
the
mall C no you're thinking of the other
one number 19 would you like a sample of
our store's newest
perfume a that's a
shame B it hasn't been released yet C
thanks I'll give it a
try number 20 when should we discuss the
business loan
application a I run a small catering
business B she would be a great asset to
us see how about meeting after
lunch number 21 could you give me a hand
preparing this presentation
slides a I have to leave early
today B someone needs to be present
there see a birthday gift from my
cousin number 22 should I put these
necklaces in the display case or hang
them by the
counter a it looks lovely on you B
she's a jewelry
designer see they should be
underglass number 23 who is organizing
the carpool for the staff
Retreat a didn't you see M Lee's
memo b I hope we go to a
resort see yes I feel like I learned a
lot
number 24 I'm surprised by the prices of
this store's
Furniture a handmade goods are always
expensive B I'd like to have it
delivered C take a seat
anywhere number 25 what kinds of
lawnmowers does your business
sell a we only rent out our
machines B it looks like New
Again C at the back of the
store number
26 how did the inspection of the
production floor go a a manufacturing
facility B that's for
sure C I haven't seen the results
number 27 didn't Nicole want to see the
final draft before it got sent for
publication a yes let's see if she's in
her
office B you can find one in the best
seller
section c the draft is coming from the
window number 28
if the post office is closed can I send
the package
tomorrow a that shouldn't be a
problem B usually on
Sundays C the address is clearly
labeled number 29 would you like to join
me at the International
Conference a do I have time to renew my
passport
b a few of the sales
people C no the last day of the
month number 30 I don't think these
colors complement each other very
well a I've only met her a few
times B don't worry we're still
deciding see that's very kind of you
number 31 why don't you include our
landlord on the guest
list a I had trouble finding the
entrance B please RSVP to my
secretary see he's already been added
[Music]
number seven did you buy this jacket at
a
discount a they're in the men's
department b a winter ski
vacation C yes it was half
off number eight who left the laptop in
the break room a no I'll keep working
B Mr Rose
did C you can borrow
mine number nine where can I pick up
luggage from flight
521 a to take a business trip B it
departs in half an
hour see at baggage carousel 3
number 10 when will the vice president
return from the board
meeting a check with his
assistant B Yes we made a lot of
decisions C in conference room
B number 11 how can I prepare for the
interview a there's a great view for
from
here B by researching the
company C she thinks she got the
job number 12 why can't I use the
parking
lot a sure except for
holidays B no I took the
bus C because it is now being repaved
number 13 are you free to cover my shift
on
Friday a I'll be out of town B who was
it C the daily specials
please number 14 what's your opinion on
the new website
design a thanks for visiting it
B no I read it in the
newspaper C I like its modern
look number 15 the light in the corridor
is still
broken a we'd better inform maintenance
again B it hasn't been decided
yet see yes we need to change our
marketing strategy
number 16 could I get a few extra
tickets for the technology
Workshop a an expert in the
field B sorry but it's sold
out see the performance was
amazing number 17 when will our banners
be ready to pick up a at least
$25 B let's call The Print Shop to
ask C oh is that what he
said number 18 this washing machine has
a water saving cycle right a I've been
watching it B at the appliance store in
the
mall C no you're thinking of the other
one number 19 would you like a sample of
our store's newest
perfume a that's a
shame B it hasn't been released yet see
thanks I'll give it a
try number 20 when should we discuss the
business loan
application a I run a small catering
business B she would be a great asset to
us see how about meeting after
lunch number 21 could you give me a hand
preparing this presentation
slides a I have to leave early
today B someone needs to be present
there sing a birthday gift from my
cousin number 22 should I put these
necklaces in the display case or hang
them by the
counter a it looks lovely on you B she's
a jewelry
designer see they should be underglass
number 23 who is organizing the carpool
for the staff
Retreat a didn't you see M Lee's
memo b I hope we go to a
resort C yes I feel like I learned a
lot number 24 I'm surprised by the
prices of this store's
Furniture a
handmade goods are always
expensive B I'd like to have it
delivered C take a seat
anywhere number 25 what kinds of
lawnmowers does your business
sell a we only rent out our
machines B it looks like New
Again C at the back of the
stall number
26 how did the inspection of the
production floor go a a manufacturing
facility B that's for
sure see I haven't seen the
results number 27 didn't Nicole want to
see the final draft before it got sent
for
publication a yes let's see if she's in
her
office B you can find one in the best
seller
section see the draft is coming from the
window number 28 if the post office is
closed can I send the package
tomorrow a that shouldn't be a problem B
usually on
Sundays C the address is clearly
labeled number 29 would you like to join
me at the International
Conference a do I have time to renew my
passport b a few of the
salese C no the last day of the month
number 30 I don't think these colors
complement each other very
well a I've only met her a few
times B don't worry we're still
deciding see that's very kind of
you number 31 why don't you include our
landlord on the guest
list a I had trouble finding the
entrance B please RSVP to my
secretary C he's already been added